Simon Fraser University Gallery fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Exhibition files, 1968-2001, predominant 1968-1987; F-90-5; 2.43 m of textual records
  - Individual exhibition files, 1968-2001, predominant 1968-1987; F-90-5-2; 2.37 m of textual records and other material; Dates: the exhibition case files (one file for each exhibition) run to 1987; after this year, there are only 2 additional files (266 and 267) containing material relating to exh
    - Bead display, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 90-9)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 1970.
    - Six Winnipeg artists, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 90-9)
      Exhibition took place between May 12-29, 1970.
      Head, Bruce; Winston Leathers; Kenneth Lochhead; Frank Mikuska; Donald Karl Reichert; Tony Tascona; Textual records
    - African art exhibition and lecturers, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 90-9)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 2 - Mar. 20, 1970.
      Jones, Abi; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Art from Poland, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Includes 19 photographs (black and white).
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Thomas Mann exhibition, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Thomas Mann; Textual records
    - Corita Kent exhibition, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 24 - Feb. 5, 1970.
      Kent, Corita; Textual records
    - Student exhibits, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Walter Piovesan; Textual records
    - Landscape / portraiture gallery west, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 31 - Apr. 17, 1970.
      Walter Ostrom; Kennedy, Garry; Jack Lemon; Baxter, Iain; Elaine Baxter; Lucy Lippard; Textual records
    - Toy - Walker - 2 part:, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between July 14-25; July 26- Aug. 7, 1970.
    - The hidden environment, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between May 12-22, 1970.
    - Computer graphics, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between May 26 - June 12, 1970.
      Mattox, Charles; Textual records
    - Computer graphics - Moose Jaw Art Museum, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Fall 1970.
      Mattox, Charles; David M. Mark; Wolf D. Rase; Rohne, Bernd; Textual records
    - H. Eric Bergman, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 24 - Dec. 18, 1970. Includes 2 photographs.
      H. Eric Bergman; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Next cloud, please!, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 22 - Oct. 9, 1970.
      Thomas Seghi; Textual records
    - Felter: 10 years, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 12-30, 1970.
    - Korean painting exhibition - Burnaby Art Gallery, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 2-20, 1970. Includes 1 photograph.
      Open, no restrictions
      Access review (Jan 24, 2023) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Eskimo graphics, 1970; F-90-5-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 2-18, 1970.
    - Exhibition program - SFU Gallery, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Spring 1971.
    - The art of the Eskimo, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 11 - Feb. 12, 1971.
    - Comics as an art form, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 16 - Mar. 5, 1971.
    - First annual British Columbia: photographers' exhibit, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 9-26, 1971.
    - Summer events, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
    - N.E. Thing Co. Ltd. display, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 30 - Apr. 16, 1971.
      N.E. Thing Co. Ltd; Textual records
    - Simon Fraser collection II, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between June 8 - July 2, 1971.
    - We caused this to be made, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between July 6-30, 1971.
      Percy, Rick; Textual records
    - Fall program, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
    - Banners, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 7-24, 1971.
      Warhol, Andy; Noland, Kenneth; Kent, Corita; Baxter, Iain; Stasik, Andrew; Carewe, Sylvia; Cornelius, Margaret; Textual records
    - Concept, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 13 - Oct. 3, 1971.
      Larry Boyce; Textual records
    - Recycled, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 90-10)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 28 - Oct. 15, 1971. Includes 6 contact sheets and 9 photographs.
    - Canadian Eskimo art, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 19 - Nov. 8, 1971.
    - Goya, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 10-26, 1971.
      Francisco Goya; Textual records
    - Dennis Hawkins, 1971; F-90-5-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 30 - Dec. 17, 1971.
      Dennis Hawkins; Textual records
    - Henry Moore, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 11-28, 1972.
      Henry Moore; Textual records
    - Exhibition program, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Spring 1972.
    - Paul Rand, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Paul Rand; Textual records
    - Second annual - BC photographers' exhibit, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
    - B.C. Crafts exhibition, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Summer and Fall 1972.
    - Ken Lochhead: recent works on paper, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between June 6-30, 1972. Inlcudes 3 negatives: b&w; 10 x 12.5 cm.
      Kenneth Lochhead; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - SF Collection: recent acquisitions, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between July 4 - Aug. 4, 1972.
    - Exhibition program, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Fall 1972.
    - John K. Esler: graphics 1963-1972, F-90-5-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 5-12, 1972. Includes 1 photographic print.
      John K. Eisler; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Oswaldo Guayasamin, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 26 - Oct. 13, 1972.
      Oswaldo Guayasamin; Textual records
    - The private patron, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 17 - Nov. 3, 1972.
    - Domingo Alvarez: infinite images, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-74; Includes 20 photographs. (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 7-17, 1972.
      Domingo Alvarez; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Tibetan Woodblock prints, 1972; F-90-5-2-0-75 (Archival box - standard 90-11)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 21 - Dec. 8, 1972.
    - Eskimo graphics 1960-1964, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-76 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 9-26, 1973.
    - China: fan paintings, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-77 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 30- Feb. 16, 1973. Includes 2 photographs.
    - Folk art of Ecuador and jungle crafts, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-78 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 20- Mar. 16, 1973. Includes 8 slides.
    - GRAFF exhibition, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-79 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 20 - Apr. 16, 1973.
    - Convocation 1973 (Alex Colville exhibit), F-90-5-2-0-80 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between May 8 - June 1, 1973. Includes 6 photographs.
      Colville, Alex; Erickson, Arthur; Smith, Gordon A.; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Vacouver LIP art, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-81 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between June 5-29, 1973. Includes 1 contact sheet, 2 photographs.
    - Recent acquisitions, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-82 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between July 3 - Aug. 12, 1973.
    - Sports in action, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-83 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between July 31 - Aug., 1973. Includes 10 negatives.
    - The Lumia recital hall, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-84 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 11-28, 1973. Includes 1 photograph.
    - British Columbia: photographer - third annual exhibit, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-85 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 2-26, 1973.
    - Roten exhibit and sale, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-86 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Ferdinand Roten Galleries, Inc.; Textual records
    - Manitoba etchings 1910-1940, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-87 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 30 - Nov. 16, 1973.
    - Joel Smith - postal paintings, 1973; F-90-5-2-0-88 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 20 - Dec. 7, 1973.
      Restricted in whole
    - Davidson Galleries sale, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-89 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 27, 1974.
      Davidson Galleries; Textual records
    - M.C. Escher: beyond reality, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-90 (Archival box - standard 90-12)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 8 - Feb. 1, 1974.
      M.C. Escher; Textual records
    - Emily Carr's contempories, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-91 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 5-22, 1974.
    - Sylvia Tait - drawings, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-92 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 226 - Mar. 15, 1974.
      Sylvia Tait; Textual records
    - Dana Atchley: fragments, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-93 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 15 - Apr. 5, 1974.
      Atchley, Dana; Textual records
    - The first year, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-94 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between May 7-31, 1974.
    - Fall exhibitions, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-95 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
    - British Columbia rugs, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-96 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between June 4-26, 1974.
    - Selections: The Simon Fraser collection, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-97 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between July 2 - Aug. 2, 1974.
    - 4th Annual - British Columbia photographers' exhibit, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-98 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 1-25, 1974.
    - Artists' stamps and stamp images, vol. 1, 1974-1979; F-90-5-2-0-99 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 1 - Nov. 15, 1974.
      Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      File has been digitized, with personal information redacted. Consult the Reference Archivist for access.
      Open: reading room only
      Reviewed for access, Jun 2021 (RD): file contains non-sensitive personal information (personal addresses from 1974). Records can be accessed in the reading room, but personal information is redacted in the digitized copy.
    - Artists' stamps and stamp images, vol. 2, 1974-1979; F-90-5-2-0-100 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Open with restricted enclosures
      File reviewed for access, Jun 2021 (RD). File contains non-sensitive personal information (personal addresses from 1977) that can be accessed in the reading room but are redacted in the digitized copy. Also includes some restricted personal information (list of prices paid to artists) that has been enclosed in the physical file and redacted in the digitized copy.
    - 50 x 50 - Dutch graphics, 1974; F-90-5-2-0-101 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 19 - Dec. 6, 1974.
    - Special events, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-102 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
    - The art of Ching-Ku Chang, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-103 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 7-24, 1975.
      Chang, Ching-Ku; Textual records
    - La Guilde Graphique, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-104 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 28 - Feb. 14, 1975.
      La Guilde Graphique; Textual records
    - Vehicule Art (Montreal) Inc., 1975; F-90-5-2-0-105 (Archival box - standard 90-13)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 18 - Mar. 14, 1975.
      Véhicule Art (Montréal) Inc.; Textual records
    - Pacific Rim consciousness, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-106 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 18 - Apr. 4, 1975. Incluces 4 contact sheets.
    - Six artists of Cape Dorset, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-107 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between May 13 - June 6, 1975. Includes 1 photograph.
    - L.L. Fitzgerald and Bertram Brooker, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-108 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between June 11 - July 6, 1975.
      L.L. Fitzgerald; Brooker, Bertram; Textual records
    - Hand coloured prints, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-109 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between July 9 - Aug. 10, 1975.
    - Recent acquisitions, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-110 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Aug. 13-29, 1975.
    - Through the first decade, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-111 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 10-26, 1975.
    - Chinese brush techniques, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-112 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 1-17, 1975.
      Jean Chaio Tsai-Tsun; Textual records
    - India: through a sociological lens, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-113 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 22 - Nov. 7, 1975.
      Sharma, Hari; Textual records
    - International Women's year, 1975; F-90-5-2-0-114 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 13 - Dec. 5, 1975.
    - Special events, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-115 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Includes 1 photograph.
    - Willem de Kooning: lithographs, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-116 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 5-23, 1976. Includes 1 photograph.
      Willem de Kooning; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Exchange / Echange, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-117 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 28 - Feb. 13, 1976.
    - Albert Dumouchel, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-118 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 18 - Mar. 5, 1976. Includes 6 photographs.
      Dumouchel, Albert; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - The art of Liang Shih-Feng, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-119 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 10-26, 1976. Includes 3 photographs.
      Liang Shih-Feng; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - German expressionist prints, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-120 (Archival box - standard 90-14)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 11 - Apr. 23, 1976.
    - The art of Frank Kocevar, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-121 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 29 - May 14, 1976. Includes 2 contact sheets and 3 photographs.
      Frank Kocevar; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Navajo blankets, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-122 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between May 17 - June 27, 1976.
    - Pitseolak retrospective, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-123 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between July 5-23, 1976. Includes 2 contact sheets and 1 photograph.
      Pitseolak; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Moments of the western world, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-124 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between July 28 - Aug. 27, 1976. Includes 22 photographs.
      Larry Stark; Addison Gallery of American Art; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Yugoslavian graphics, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-125 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 7 - Oct. 1, 1976. Includes 1 photo.
    - Hygiene of art - Herve Fischer, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-126 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 12 - Nov. 5, 1976.
      Hervé Fischer; Textual records
    - Saskatchewan photography, 1976; F-90-5-2-0-127 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 15 - Dec. 10, 1976. Includes 3 photographs.
    - Changing visions - landscapes 1977, F-90-5-2-0-128 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 2-25, 1977.
    - Imogen Cunningham - photographs, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-129 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 10-28, 1977.
      Imogen Cunningham; Textual records
    - Johnson S.S. Chow: Chinese painting, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-130 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Johnson S.S. Chow; Textual records
    - White sculpture of the Inuit, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-131 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 7-25, 1977. Includes 11 photographs and 2 contact sheets.
    - Kathie Kollwitz: prints, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-132 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 6-29, 1977.
      Käthe Kollwitz; Textual records
    - Robert Motherwell - selected prints, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-133 (Archival box - standard 90-15)
      Exhibition took place between May 4 - June 10, 1977.
      Robert Motherwell; Textual records
    - Two from Newfoundland, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-134 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between June 20 - July 8, 1977. Includes 1 contact sheet.
      Frank Lapointe; Gerald Squires; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Group of Seven and their contemporaries, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-135 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between July 18 - Aug. 5, 1977. Includes 1 contact sheet.
    - Ester Warkov: drawings, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-136 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Aug. 15 - Sept. 9, 1977.
      Ester Warkov; Textual records
    - Some aspects of head and figure: from the Imperial Oil Art Collection, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-137 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 19 - Oct. 7, 1977. Includes 1 contact sheet.
      Imperial Oil Ltd.; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Royal Watercolour Society, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-138 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 17 - Nov. 4, 1977.
      Royal Society of Painters in Water-Colours; Textual records
    - Ukiyo-E: Japanese prints, 1977; F-90-5-2-0-139 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 14 - Dec. 2, 1977. Includes 1 photograph.
    - Exhibitions, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-140 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
    - Process and transformation: eleven American photographers, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-141 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 9- 27, 1978. Includes 2 photographs.
    - Recent acquisitions, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-142 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 6- 24, 1978.
    - J. Frederic McCulloch, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-143 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 6- 31, 1978.
      J. Frederick McCullogh; Textual records
    - Captain James Cook, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-144 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 10- 30, 1978.
      James Cook; Department of History; Textual records
    - Madam Ho Chao Iwa: Chinese painting, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-145 (Archival box - standard 90-16)
      Exhibition took place between May 8-26, 1978.
      Ho Chao Hwa; Textual records
    - Feliciano Bejar, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-146 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between June 5-30, 1978. Includes 6 photographs.
      Béjar, Feliciano; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Jack Wise - a decade of work, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-147 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between July 10-28, 1978.
      Jack Wise; Textual records
    - Women in art, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-148 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between Aug. 7-18, 1978.
    - Richard Kostelanetz, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-149 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between Sept. 11-29, 1978. 1 photograph.
      Richard Kostelanetz; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Mark Anderson - sculpture, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-150 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between Aug. 2 - Sept. 29, 1978. Includes 3 contact sheets.
      Mark Anderson; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - The Artists of Cape Dorset, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-151 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 27, 1978.
    - Contemporary Canadian images, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-152 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 6-24, 1978.
    - New Testament narratives, 1978; F-90-5-2-0-153 (Archival box - standard 90-17)
      Exhibition took place between Dec. 4-22, 1978.
      E.B. Crocker Art Gallery; Textual records
    - The inner eye of Chen Chi-Kwan, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-154 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 8-26, 1979.
      Chen Chi-Kwan; Textual records
    - The art of lithography, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-155 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Feb. 7-23, 1979. Includes 3 photographs.
    - Jasper Johns / screenprints, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-156 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Apr. 9 - May 11, 1979.
      Jasper Johns; Textual records
    - Native Canadian graphics, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-157 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Mar. 5-30, 1979.
    - Graficas: Latin American prints, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-158 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between June 18 - July 13, 1979.
    - Images of the Inuit, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-159 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between July 23 - Aug. 17, 1979.
    - Herbert Bayer: photographic works, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-160 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Aug 27 - Sept. 21, 1979.
      Herbert Bayer; Textual records
    - Drawings by Jack Weldon Humphrey, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-161 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Oct. 1-26, 1979.
      Jack Weldon Humphrey; Textual records
    - Szeto, Kei and Nigel, 1979; F-90-5-2-0-162 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Nov. 5-23, 1979.
      Kei Szeto; Nigel Szeto; Textual records
    - Les Manning - ceramics, 1980; F-90-5-2-0-163 (Archival box - standard 90-18)
      Exhibition took place between Jan. 7-25, 1980. Includes 1 photograph.
      Les Manning; Textual records; Photographic materials